[{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980376818,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":32365,"timeElapsed":177252},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980399050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":22230,"timeElapsed":199484},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":6542,"timeElapsed":206028},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980423090,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":17494,"timeElapsed":223524},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":16782,"timeElapsed":240308},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980453554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":13679,"timeElapsed":253988},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":13607,"timeElapsed":267596},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980482010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":14847,"timeElapsed":282444},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980501938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"145","question":"Describe the most recent gift you received. Who was it from and what was the context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":19927,"timeElapsed":302372},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":58975,"timeElapsed":364612},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5446,"timeElapsed":370060},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575554,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":5926,"timeElapsed":375988},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980585378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":9823,"timeElapsed":385812},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980599858,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":14479,"timeElapsed":400292},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980612402,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":12543,"timeElapsed":412836},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980622034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":9630,"timeElapsed":422468},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":9838,"timeElapsed":432308},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980646906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"217","question":"Do you commute to work or work from home? If you commute, how do you usually get there (for example, by car, bus, bicycle)? How long does it take? If you work from home, do you have a room set aside just for work?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":15031,"timeElapsed":447340},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980665274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":15775,"timeElapsed":465708},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980670370,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":5094,"timeElapsed":470804},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980674618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4247,"timeElapsed":475052},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980701466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":26847,"timeElapsed":501900},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980715922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":14455,"timeElapsed":516356},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980729154,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":13231,"timeElapsed":529588},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980740298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":11143,"timeElapsed":540732},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980753122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":12823,"timeElapsed":553556},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980765418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":12295,"timeElapsed":565852},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980782098,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":14999,"timeElapsed":582532},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980787162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5063,"timeElapsed":587596},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980813362,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":26199,"timeElapsed":613796},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":5886,"timeElapsed":619684},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":17191,"timeElapsed":636876},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980849026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":95,"rt":12582,"timeElapsed":649460},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980864946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":15919,"timeElapsed":665380},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980879562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":14615,"timeElapsed":679996},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980893418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":13855,"timeElapsed":693852},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980905922,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"242","question":"Do you have any creative hobbies? Do you create art? Describe these hobbies or activities.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":12503,"timeElapsed":706356},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980931298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":23735,"timeElapsed":731732},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980936970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":5671,"timeElapsed":737404},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981028682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":91710,"timeElapsed":829116},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981040530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":11847,"timeElapsed":840964},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981064026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":23495,"timeElapsed":864460},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981068178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4151,"timeElapsed":868612},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981073146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":4966,"timeElapsed":873580},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981077114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":877548},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981080362,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3247,"timeElapsed":880796},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981136290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":54727,"timeElapsed":936724},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981141770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5479,"timeElapsed":942204},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981148178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":6407,"timeElapsed":948612},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981156170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":7990,"timeElapsed":956604},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981166602,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":10431,"timeElapsed":967036},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981177939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":11335,"timeElapsed":978373},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981183322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":5381,"timeElapsed":983756},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981191970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":8647,"timeElapsed":992404},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981199946,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"90","question":"What kinds of predicaments are you best at giving advice about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":7974,"timeElapsed":1000380},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981213210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":11863,"timeElapsed":1013644},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981218338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5126,"timeElapsed":1018772},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981227586,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":9247,"timeElapsed":1028020},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981252530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":24943,"timeElapsed":1052964},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981265250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":12718,"timeElapsed":1065684},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981281074,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":15823,"timeElapsed":1081508},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981295290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":14215,"timeElapsed":1095724},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981309026,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13735,"timeElapsed":1109460},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981328274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"194","question":"Do you have a favorite band or musical genre? Describe either.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":19247,"timeElapsed":1128708},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981386906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":55103,"timeElapsed":1187340},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981393522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6614,"timeElapsed":1193956},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981398170,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4647,"timeElapsed":1198604},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981409938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":11767,"timeElapsed":1210372},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981421378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":11439,"timeElapsed":1221812},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981438034,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":16655,"timeElapsed":1238468},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981461546,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":23511,"timeElapsed":1261980},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981474938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13390,"timeElapsed":1275372},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981484427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"28","question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":9487,"timeElapsed":1284861},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981495034,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When did you last cry in front of another person? By yourself?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":10606,"timeElapsed":1295468},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981505618,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":9151,"timeElapsed":1306052},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981509290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3671,"timeElapsed":1309724},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981513066,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3775,"timeElapsed":1313500},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981519474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":6407,"timeElapsed":1319908},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981540883,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":21407,"timeElapsed":1341316},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981548642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":7758,"timeElapsed":1349076},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981554218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5575,"timeElapsed":1354652},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981562186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":7967,"timeElapsed":1362620},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981571218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":9031,"timeElapsed":1371652},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981585218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":12647,"timeElapsed":1385652},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981593186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":7967,"timeElapsed":1393620},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981604914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":11727,"timeElapsed":1405348},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981613970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9055,"timeElapsed":1414404},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981623986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":10015,"timeElapsed":1424420},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981639290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":15303,"timeElapsed":1439724},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981650658,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":11367,"timeElapsed":1451092},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981664611,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":13951,"timeElapsed":1465045},{"subjectID":"rfelnd79aq","prolificID":"675ff99a4bf03b67e8a31e40","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b23edaa828312e3e7cf3","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981695106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"170","question":"What is the longest you have gone without checking your phone?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":30495,"timeElapsed":1495540}]